We were young and naive but I thought we could control it
But then life took me for a ride
You went and I spiraled forward
Handing down as my life lost its purpose
I was without my way
I lost my faith in a downward spiral
And now I start to rebuild it
Build it in a circle
I lost my way
My faith in a downward spiral
I watch my life wither away
In the gutter where I pray
A thousand miles on the open road
Blackened sky, story untold
If I listen to my dreams
If I hear you in my sleep
If I scream into my fears
Would you listen to it all?
But the world kept me again
And again and again
I can never seem to die
I'm the unlucky and they're lucky
I watch my life wither away
In the gutter where I pray
A thousand miles on the open road
Blackened sky, story untold
I watch my life wither away
I lost my faith