In his hand, the notes said, alas a prophecy to heed in time.
Set there is a rhythm to a rhyme, a rhyme to a rhythm a key to unwind the flaws between your bars and your lines
p..p...poison gas, the riddle's last riddle blows past the joker's last laugh HAAA
If crazy I'd be then I'd be freed of all reason so no point believing that hatred you're squeezing
So shut your mouth or it'll get beaten when I tear off your sheet to reveal the true heathen
You're in need of parental suspension of the over-abundance of attention
Mama should've taught you to hide that micro-erection
Consider this your cranially retentive mental health intervention
Pre-flight inspection to reveal a spinal hyperextension that finally gave way
Now boarding, one through nine, session
Consider this your cranially retentive mental health intervention
Now boarding, one through nine, interception
What does it mean to be me?
Am I a hero or am I a demon's dream?
Born to be a hero but I still got that demon scene
One through nine, read the display, black monochrome reflection
We're in transit to the fray of inception so trays up, seats back, this is the finale
Your final destination, you're a state of unreal it seems
Forever stuck in sucking life's long punctuated fallacy
But damn, man's duality is a two-sided boat, notes burning in a sea of right and wrong
You see a nice part of me, a truce of one but the other truce sees no sea
Paired to intersect thee, he or she will be or not to be
Throwing down no no holds bared scared straight barometry
Gravitate implicit forces all on me
Run, run, fight, you fit to fight, but fled left when heroes run right
A coward, All talk, no bite, fright the knight
I raided all night pretending, still stuck benching
Quit night, shit night, you not wrenching
Oh, your balls are not descending, impending
You're pulling up stuff, crated, ruled, not descending
Inside you ignited, a swollen engulf
In flames of contagious, contagion of failures
Fucking fall in rage, so rage on, son
So soon you'll be baited with the rage and hatred you're spraying
Constant inconsistence, we go with that which is so faded
The lathe, yes, I go, now you're flated
Seem to stay here
Just change it, that's all what you got
That's all what you said and that what you want
That's all what the world has got when it lives
That's what we all got left to give