I'm not sick of this world, I'm just so sick of the pain
Before I do something stupid and I open a vein
I put a bottle to my head to inject vodka to the brain
I cry out, but demons call back my name I'm supposed to be silent, strong, and always
in frame But what should I do when I can't calm the
rage?
It burns as it starts to spread the craze A poison's fired and I'm this pain
I want to be sober and someday I may But I may just need to exit the cage
My body's on the thunder now as the last breath of the brain
I black out, I drink, I drink, I drink, I drink until I'm insane
No thoughts of tomorrow, I'm wretched and stained
I'll break down and pray, please, please, please Help me be strong to find better days
I know it's sobriety or it's one foot in the grave
All over morning, my headache enraged Like it's raining down raises as I wait for
the blame I've got so much to lose and so little to
gain So be brave, be brave, and be sober and pray
I wrote this verse a little too late The one I was trying to save has already sealed
their fate But I'm still out here slinging some words
and lyrics Cause maybe I'll reach somebody out there
still ringing Maybe their phone's still there, there's
still time to save them There's still somewhere out there in the
cold darkness The world can be so fucking cruel, just darkness
and rain I understand you're out there with the pain
and the pain and the pain The one I was trying to save has already
sealed their fate
All over morning, my headache enraged Like it's raining down raises as I wait for
the blame I've got so much to lose and so little to
gain So be brave, be brave, and be sober and pray
There's still time to save them There's still somewhere out there in the
cold darkness The world can be so fucking cruel, just darkness
and rain I understand you're out there with the pain
and the pain and the pain But there's usually someone, someone that
would've helped you if they'd only known But you didn't tell them cause you need to
tell them Cause then you don't have to walk that fucking
road on your own Just pick up that goddamn phone
I wrote this song slaying some words instead of going back in time
Cause I would've helped by just getting through anything but instead
There's still time to save them There's still somewhere out there in the
cold darkness The world can be so fucking cruel, just darkness
and rain I understand you're out there with the pain
and the pain and the pain But there's usually someone, someone that
would've helped you if they'd only known But you didn't tell them cause you need to
tell them Cause then you don't have to walk that fucking
road on your own Just pick up that goddamn phone
I wrote this song slaying some words instead of going back in time
Cause I would've helped by just getting through anything but instead
There's still time to save them There's still somewhere out there in the
cold darkness The world can be so fucking cruel, just darkness
and rain I understand you're out there with the pain
and the pain and the pain But there's usually someone, someone that
would've helped you if they'd only known But you didn't tell them cause you need to
tell them Cause then you don't have to walk that fucking
road on your own Just pick up that goddamn phone
I wrote this song slaying some words instead of going back in time
Cause I would've helped by just getting through anything but instead
There's still time to save them There's still somewhere out there in the
cold darkness The world can be so fucking cruel, just darkness
and rain I understand you're out there with the pain
and the pain and the pain But there's usually someone, someone that
would've helped you if they'd only known But you didn't tell them cause you need to
tell them Cause then you don't have to walk that fucking
road on your own Just pick up that goddamn phone
I wrote this song instead of going back in time
Cause I would've helped by just getting through anything but instead
There's still time to save them There's still somewhere out there in the cold