It's a Friday and I'm all alone Thinking what I might do when I come and see you
And then I hear that you're back Rebounding and all of that
But what a night to go Go get that chance back
To find the fire we once knew To see it right and make it through
Can we ever make this right? Can we be fire, fire
Fire on a Friday night
Hotter than a fire fight I saw you and I know you'll see me too
It felt like you were miles away But now you're right there, back to where I knew
I knew you'd make it here someway, somehow But I didn't think I'd find a way
Catch the fire we once had To feel the heat as it burns inside
I'm hotter than a fire fight I can't escape once the flame is caught within my sight
Fire, fire
It's fire on a Friday night
You got that fire, fire
Hotter than a fire fight
And we're chasing after something that we just cannot contain
The fire that it burns inside the sea and just don't flame
It's a desire that we just cannot attain
Just chasing after something if we can just obey
Keep that fire alive
We're on a journey, dreams are hard following our dreams
No matter where they start Driven by a fire, the fire that burns deep within
We're unstoppable, we're driven by a fire that it burns so deep within
We're unstoppable, unbreakable
We're reaching for the stars, we're chasing out our wildest whim
We're unstoppable, our mission a team to get the whim
We're unstoppable, unbreakable on fire
It's so hot, it is my fire
My fire on a Friday, a Friday night
When you walked back into my little life
I thought I had it all on lockdown and everything was tame
Then I saw you light that fire on me, that Friday game
Cause fire, fire
Your fire on a Friday night