I don't want to hear about tomorrow or any other day
Babe, can we just go out to party like a wave?
A dance wave, hips movin', layin' down, body hangin', dance breakin', dance party
Everybody say okay, dance great, live for the day, live great, party, party, dance Cray
I don't want to hear about tomorrow or any other day
Live now, party hard, dance great, live now, party hard, dance cray
Body rock, body shot, head sway, night is in the night, dance cray
I don't want to hear about tomorrow or any other day
Dance great, tonight we dancin', body out, dance great
Body rock, body shot, head sway, dance cray
Dance cray, tonight we dancin', body out, dance cray
Dance great, tonight we dancin', body hard, dance great
Dance great, dance great, dance great, dance great
Make it louder, don't say, live for today
Dance great, dance great, body out, live now, dance great
I don't want to hear about tomorrow or any other day
Live now, party hard, dance cray, we don't stop at the clock
No matter what you say, party hard, you're not gonna touch the grave
We won't stop at the clock or any say in the morning, underneath the grave
Body rock, head shot, head sway, party dance cray
Under the grave, every day, live now, be free
Party hard, dance cray
I won't stop the clock or any other way, party hard or live free
This is the night, we don't stop at the clock no matter what you say
Party hard all night till the grave
We won't stop the clock or any say
Run and run, run and run, run and run till the grave, dance night, dance all night, party out
Dance great, matter of the grave, to dance cray
Communicate my dance craze
Dance craze
Dance cray