Do you even mean the nice things?
What you said when we had ice cream Are relationships in tatters
And you still throw dark matter With your words cut deep like daggers
My heart is fully shattered You say the most awful things to me
Verbal abuse is not my scene Nothing fucking matters if you're mean
Cause nothing fucking matters Nothing fucking matters
Nothing fucking matters if you're mean Verbal abuse is not my scene
Cause nothing fucking matters if you're mean
I love it when you're loving So sweet and overcoming
But I can't keep on shoving When you beat me down I'm numbing
Yes we've made a come up And I love it when we make up
But all these insults keep beating me down And I can't keep shoving down
My feelings of disgust As you keep trying to hurt us
It's like you're critiquing every single thing Every way I do anything at all
And I can't take this anymore Cause nothing fucking matters if you're mean
I know that I'm not perfect And I probably deserve it
But that doesn't mean it's worth it For you to insult me like you do
It's just a dozen wishes, a loving spark All it does is make me wanna leave
Nothing fucking matters if you're mean Cause nothing fucking matters
Nothing fucking matters if you're mean Cause nothing fucking matters if you're mean
You're mean, you're mean Cause nothing fucking matters if you're mean
Verbal abuse is not my sin