Take a walk in the dark, take a walk in the darkness
Everything dark but your eyes
Is this our moment
When we see what's inside
My love, my hair, our heart in our bed
Are we sleeping inside
At night, our pain, our hearts, our sweat
Are they trapped in a bed of lies
Oh, our love, our love is all here
That's filled with the word of lies
But I lay here before you in the night
Lying dead by the side
And you both know the ride
If you're ready, you can hear it inside
Because I know
The stories of our lives
Even when we cry
I know
We're all frozen inside
Our love, our love is all here
That's filled with the word of lies
If you're ready, you can hear it inside
Because I know
Maybe
Even when the bed of lies
My love
We're all frozen inside