Rise above a mindless trace And find a way to save the base
We're creators brave the artist's face Hollow waves refrained with grit
We plug it, we fuck it, we make it fit We fierce the face of fearless wits
So fuck the haters and post that shit
I'm out the fog, gray of ace Most wheels popped off its corporate case
An al-Qad without the mushy and graced Afraid of roaming up the pace
Defy the new and up the space We out the lurkers, rest in place
We're passing through the new found places And out the ways to raise the base
And out the lurkers, rest in case
Caught talent's eye with a forge that's lit This rag ran high but the city blitz
Sky does fall, sounds all of it So drop the lines, drip by drop by drip
To make it fit, we fierce the face of fearless wits
So fuck the haters and post that shit
I'm out the drip by drop by drip by drop land
An artist cries of tears telling it's been
Drip by drop by drip by drop land An artist cries of tears telling it's been
Catch me cam, my inspiration chase I ain't afraid, fear not man nor man has
made No humiliation, all a race
I stand up to eject or embrace To take the spotlight and craze
The days, days, days, the day's light
I'm balls to the wall, hard work with no rest
When I'm down I tell time to regress Before I go I reset the saloon
Rip off the riptide, spend it flow Head to head, toe to coat red
Ripple through the carrots, I got a flag
What? Drink this with coffee, we made you awake
Proud be the artist, your name, the namesake Pillagers, ignite the game, shake and trace
Like a canine's bite or a freak in the base Ain't no inspo from a derivative lease
Like a stalker's echo, so loud we would creep it
Huddled around so closely, we'd deep it Proud be the battle hymn sung from the glade pit
Turn off the ground, just churned on the grave bit
Oh, take a hold of it, sit there, we're gonna throw down low
I feel that we sound low, the whole bit by bit
Quick slip, the lyrical visitor we mix
First cringe, triple record, we racked up, we sing
We spun, ends undone, we record, we sung
I know I won, fantastic stones, no red bones
But I'm by our stop and follow
Unite the creative powers and take it all on
But together we got this, the red light's gone
Turn off, then turn on, go, but not gone
Hollow, we left or right, but we're strong
Life beyond, not what it'd be
But a lesson beyond, we're emotional trees
We're only subtle calm, from storms, break brains, freeze
Life is a game, so players play tight
I feel the beams, our creators create their own light
This is the journey and it's own plight
If your life is the plane