All I am and all I need is all I ever wanted
And smile and scream and feel the pain
And when the time is energy, all you need becomes love, all you need becomes sound
How do I get past this point to have those dreams we never had?
I don't know what this path leads, but all this pain is killing me
At first I loved the excitement, but I cannot live in your violence
Toxic swings that fuck off the silence, no, I cannot live in your violence
Oh, oh, why do we say it'll be alright
When there's no doubt the end is fast, it's all pain and broken hearts
Shattered dreams and false starts, can we go away from here?
I hold the memory of life so dear, I want to say so many things but I'm stuck in a lie
I want to know where the end goes when you leave and go
It's exciting, I can no longer take the pain, I cannot live in your violence