As I lay my soul to bare You just sit there with pretty hair
Is all this talk just in vain Am I a shadow in the rain
All this love goes down the drain I'm a shadow in the rain
Lost in my thoughts, can't shake the past I try to move on but it's never gonna last
Stuck in a cycle, can't escape the pain I'm just a shadow in the rain
I'm reaching out but no one cares So fuck it all, there's no one there
I'm just a ghost in an empty space Memory, a forgotten place
As I lay my soul to bare You just sit there with pretty hair
Is all this talk just in vain As my life goes down the drain
Just a shadow in the rain I'm just a shadow
I'm just a shadow in the rain Drowning in our memory
Lost in darkness, so it seems Can't find a way out
Stuck in time, reflection of a love that died I'm reaching out but no one cares
So fuck it all, there's no one there I'm just a ghost in this empty space
A memory, forgotten place As I lay my soul to bare
You just sit there with pretty hair Is this talk all in vain
Is there something more to say I'm a shadow in the rain
Just a shadow in the rain I'm a shadow in the rain
I search for answers in a world so cold This broken heart is getting old
I wanna play but I'm forced to fold I don't know where the story holds
Will this end right, will it go Is this all I have to show
Will I be okay on my own?
As I lay my soul to bare You just sit there with pretty hair
Is all this talk just in vain Am I a shadow in the rain?
All this love goes down the drain I'm a shadow in the rain
I'm a shadow in the rain