As long as we're living like we're living our last dreams
We don't care what anyone has got to say
Just love each other every day
Cause me and you, and you and me
In this fantasy
Cause I love you and you love me
And we love to say I love you
Even in our stupid popcorn dreams, I say I love you too
I love you, l-l-l-love you
In our little fantasy, like we're living our last dream
Fantasy world, I can be your boy and you can be my girl
My lady, it's handsomely together for the world
Handsomely, like we're living out our last dream
In our fantasy world, ecstasy guaranteed
Like we're living our last dream, easily, we laughily
Playing sauce against the world
Like we're living our last dream
Like we're living our last dream, easily, we laughily
Playing sauce against the world
And you know, like it's living our last dream
You don't even have to say it, I can see
But I know you like to say you love me
I love you, even in our popcorn dreams
I'll always say I love you too
That's me and you
I love it, I love how cheesily we can be
And all our care is given
Cause it's us against the world
In our fantasy dream
My lady, and I'm your majesty
Or is it me, a gallant dream
Calvary, it's at your side
Oh, I sit here and I make believe
That we and you have seen
Like we're living our last dream
Easily, we laughily
Playing sauce against the world
Like it's living our last dream
Like we both took ecstasy
It's so vivid, it's so perfect, you and me
Cause it's my lady, or is it my majesty