On a lonely road alone, I hear the wind that blows
It's cold and empty feeling, but I keep on moving
On a lonely road alone, I'm searching for a way to call my home
I don't know where I'm going, but I'll keep, keep, keep on moving
Keep on moving
I've been down this road before, I've seen the darkness of the storm
But I won't, but I won't let it get me, I'll keep moving, moving on
On a lonely road alone, searching for ways to call my home
I don't know where I'm going, but I'll keep moving
There are days when I feel lost, days when I wonder what's the cause
But I won't give up the fight, not that easily I might
But I gotta keep moving, moving, moving on
On a lonely road alone, searching for a way to call my home
But I know, I don't know where I'm going, I'm lost without reason
But I won't stop believing, so I'll keep on moving, I'll keep on moving on
On a lonely road alone
And I search, and I search, and I search, I know, for the reason to call this searching home
And I know, cause I know, cause I know, I don't know where I'm going
But I'll still be believing that if I keep on moving, and just keep moving
Then one day, I'll see beyond the storm
Cause I'm still here, and I'm still going
For a world after all this, I can't let it hit me
Cause I'm on a lonely road alone, and I'm searching for a way home
Cause I know