I open and see that bricks to me Drop some beats for anyone to rap on these
So I said, what the fuck, and take a freeze And try to freestyle rap and drop some D's
I'm going back to the fucking metal So let's drop some bars right on this trap
Track the golden juice cause we know how to let loose
So let's meta this rap and stop the grease King of the trap, trap royalty
I'm living lavish and free I ain't doing this for us, I'm doing it for
me Cause I was the one who always believed in
the talent that I seem to see Even though the haters can't stop fucking with
me I don't care if they go
They got no fucking face, they got no fucking point
No brains, no talent, no waste They're a waste of a soul
Their life's down the drain All they are is life, living in pain
But I'm trap royalty, lavish and free And I don't give a fuck, the haters mean nothing
to me You mean nothing to me
Like an ant, a squirm, a nasty fuckazee Slugs, a dirty fucking bitch, shut up and
fuzz me Cause I keep trying to be me
And I don't give a fuck if it's talent you see
Cause I'm trap royalty Cause this beat was king of the trap
And I fucking jump on it to freestyle rap And I match the beat and I match the intention
I'm going fuck like a hard ass rection I'm good enough
I open and see, fix the main Drop the beat for anyone to strap and freeze
So I thought I would freeze and try to give it some trap
I don't normally sing that style but I understand The fundamentals of how to fucking rap
So let's drop the shit, drop it right on the track
Turn it up, the title to a golden key To live life like we got it, so let's go for
King of the trap, trap royalty I'm living lavish and free
I ain't doing this for us, I'm doing it for me
Cause I was the one who always believed in the talent that I seem to see
Even though the haters can't stop fucking with me
I don't care if they go I'm the one on top, ain't one to scold
But I never go out, fuck you and fools Ain't no power to hold the powers that be
I'm in control cause I'm the one who does me
I don't have to listen to what the fuck you say or what you see
Cause I am me, the king is thee King of the trap, so I am me
The throne, what they see Cause I am me and the king is thee
So why am I trap royalty?