I can't figure it out How you got me going upside inside out
My heart is going downside upside now Round and round and round
Now I can't figure this out My heart is full of doubt
As it goes upside outside in Round and round upside downside now
My heart is beating loud I try to keep my head above the water
But my heart is like a son and daughter Fighting for the upper hand
It leaves me out in no man's land I can't figure this out
My head is full of doubt Beating to the ground
While my heart is spinning round Round and round and round
I'm feeling outside inside out Downside upside now
My heart is spinning upside downside out My heart is beating loud
Spinning round and round Round and round and round
I used to think we had it all together But now I think our love is like a tether
Holding on to what's left From a love that once was so deaf
My head stuck in the cloud I'm looking out
Tomorrow will bring a change Maybe love will come my way
Until then I can say My heart is going round
Round and round and round My heart goes upside inside out
Downside inside now My heart is going upside inside out
Downside upside now My heart is