Can it be? Can this get any better than it seems?
Or is this the top of what life's supposed to be?
I don't know
If all I have is one more day, I'd spend it home with you
Instead of traveling, let's snuggle up and watch some S.F.
If I had a moment, I'd just smile and say
That I'm so happy that I get to spend my final day with you
With you, with you, I always knew
That I could see this whole thing through
Love and love, our love is true
Me and you, forever two
We're on our way, my love
The time's just passing by
I'm breathing what you smell like
As our lives intertwine
All alone I was before I saw you
Sitting there, divine
All I know is that our love
Till the end of time
With you, with you, I always knew
That I could see this whole thing through
Love and love, our love is true
Me and you, forever two
With you, with you, I always knew
That I could see this whole thing through
All alone I was before I saw you
Sitting there, divine
Love before the end of all
Love before the end of all time
We're on our way, my love
The time's just passing by
I'm breathing what you smell like
As our lives intertwine
All alone I was before I saw you
Sitting there, divine
All I know is that our love
Till the end of time
Time, time, time, time
Saw you on the laundry mat
Stuffing your last dollar
In the machine trying to get out
The spilled pasta from last night