When you feel it, you just gotta goooooo
Always thinking though, sometimes I think I should just stay apolitical
Or is that really just a sign of being typical?
My cold and clean flow, it's almost clinical
Like execution row, time is critical
Whack it to a winning spree
Drive one back and roast in threes
Backyard BBQ on your knees
Open wide while I proselytize thee
That means analyze your verse for free
Breaking the fourth wall, hi it's me
Your music's al the same, same rhyme, same lame refrain
Never wang, just hem, just whip strained and drained
From an amateur gone insane, no manners
Isn't it a crime to never utilize more than 10% of the grey matter in your brain?
Your tumor ruling, jelly brain in a fried cranium
Starving coffin dwelling, fried green tomatoes
Sam, I am green, isn't I am brain?
I think I'm experiencing an melow dramatic loss of memory
Like voter recall
Anyways, you should cover your assonates in it
It's lackening, flattening, top heavy, split in sections
No comment, back to nonsense rhymes
It kinda makes sense at the end
Where the vented scents are actually gathered and spent
Sat on to you but rejected by those dejected by poetic minds
With a sense of stench of a poor performance
Who realize that lines that won't even sell cents
Don't make sense to play post-secondary school
What?
A slobbering bag of gruel
Is what's offered to pay the pack
A pack of another author's back
Garnished with never-ending lies
You ready here?
I declare
Your one-backed rose to be
Back your baby-kew on your knees
Open wide while I proselytize these
Leveled up
At the ending phase
Power plays
To raise the stakes
1,000 heroes in a million plays
Cause the hero's birth is the one that pays
Leveled up
At the ending phase
Hero's birth is the one that pays
Thousand heroes in a million plays
Cause the hero's bear is the one that pays
Leveled up, the end is near
We begin a revolution on a whim and a care
To put forth musical comprehension
The prayer to the throne is rare as intellectual ascension
Neither truth nor crooked dare
Could break the masses of the unwavering stare
Unfair, can't I unravel the farthest tales of a person's worth
Like a ship's abode sinking alone
Foretold as waves the ocean comes forth
Calling poisonous all notions that the noise has been missed
You miss the musty air and the quickness of steam from the sinking ocean
You are besieged, you feel the ocean
But the rest of this world is down to the sink
This is a temporal message of
Hurrying you down to the ocean
Please don't stop staring at the air
The ocean, the breath, the arms, don't stop it
This is the end
Leveled up, the end defends
The power flames to raise the sails
Though this ain't a passing maze
But a wave of forked decays
Silhouettes step down in tragic plays
Play for play, the underdogs raise the stage
It stays black but never fades
We extinguish the brightest blade, darkness
To the end of days
Aha, slowly fade away
What the fuck am I talking about?
Run, this ain't a passing maze
But a fork stuck in different ways
Solve it with a secret phrase
Don't graze me, bro
Kill not taze