We've come a long way in such a short time, but even now
Sometimes it feels like the world is against me
Sometimes it feels like I'm never enough Sometimes it feels like I'm running on empty
And I realise you're already with me So it's never too rough
And we will never give up We'll be strong and we'll be brave
We won't let them get in our way No stick together, make it through
We don't need no one but me and you, me and you
I know I'm not the only one having trouble I know I'm not the only one seeing double,
seeing double I know I'm not the only one to say I can't
go on without time Time to get through this weather
Time to rough it up and be the better Time to realise that with you
We'll always find a way to stick through We don't need anyone else right now
We'll be strong and we'll be brave We won't let them get in our way
We'll stick together, make it through We don't need anyone but me and you, me and
you Sometimes it feels like the road is too long
Sometimes it feels like I just don't belong Sometimes it feels like we're living
We don't give up or end We keep going till the end
We'll be strong and we'll be brave We won't let them get in our way
We'll stick together, make it through We don't need anyone but me and you, me and
you We'll be strong and we'll be brave
We won't let them get in our way We'll stick together, make it through
We don't need anyone but me and you, me and you