Agility
I have the agility and phonic ability to rhyme each syllable in trilogy
And the humility to perceive the futility of trying to rhyme from a lyrical shooting spree
Danger's immune to me, that's an untrue fact
But what I have achieved is para-rhyme consonance mastery
So you damn me can't teach you to compare you to me
Rap singing, sing the flow and let it roll and go
And let it flip off your tongue and then when you're done it goes right back out we go
Now it's time to fucking diss, the rappers stop crunching in a cultural abyss
They're slurring their words and it can barely make sense
That you can't stand the stench, your bars so sloppy they have no pretext
I think deeper to refer it's own intention, long before they got monotone
A self mediocrity, there is a class on sucking life's empathy
Their sounds still wonder what it means to me, like they echo in silence
Not symmetry, not symmetry, as perhaps caused by a brain freeze telemetry
They're the ones who chop down the giving tree
So let's see, they're a hoppy wailing on two skinnies, you're a clown, a class two leffy
Ah, the one that's named in the toilet seat, gibberish or sharpie
Now it's time to fucking diss, the rappers stop crunching in a cultural abyss
They're slurring their words and it can barely make sense
That you can't stand the stench, your bars so sloppy they have no pretext
Now it's time to fucking diss, the rappers stop crunching in a cultural abyss
They're slurring their words and it can barely make sense
Punch drunk, I can still rap straight lines from a Shakespearean soliloquy
No seriously, I talk to myself all day for free
And I'll break the fourth wall, whenever I please
Aye, it's me